During this course, we're going to play with a no code programming interface called Node-RED.
It's very common nowadays to use it for IoT projects.
We'll mostly use it to create an IoT platform. To install NodeRED.
We're going to use Docker.
So we go on the Docker Hub website where we can find all the available services for Docker and we look
for the NodeRED service.
This one is deprecated, so we're going to use this one.
We just need to copy the command and that's it.
Let's execute that in our terminal.
On the left we've got a mobaXTerm terminal and on the right we have Docker Desktop running.
I execute the command I've copied previously and when everything has been downloaded, I can see that
a new container has been created locally on my Docker Desktop interface.
I can now connect to it with my web browser localhost.
1880.
Here we are.
We are now ready to play with it.
And if you want to turn it off, then you just need to stop it from the Docker interface.
Don't worry if you don't know how to use it.
Of course.
We'll explain everything.